

CONTACT



Birthdate: January 14, 1996 | 27 yrs. old





Mail:

neontolentino@gmail.com



anthonytolentino14.000webhostapp.com



Address:

I. Dejoya St., Dejoya Bayview Subd Cuta, Batangas City Batangas

SKILLS

- Technical Troubleshooting and Problem
- Resolution
- Hardware and Software Installation,

Configuration, and Maintenance

- Network Administration and Security
- Help Desk Support and Incident

Management

- User Training and Documentation
- Active Directory and Exchange

Management

- Windows OS Support
- ITIL Framework and Best Practices
- Excellent Communication and Customer

Service

- · Experience in implementing and managing backup solutions
- Collaborated with cross-functional

teams to implement system upgrades.

- Capability to work collaboratively with
- cross-functional teams
- Willingness to stay updated with the latest industry trends.

Anthony **Tolentino**

IT Support Representative

OBJECTIVE:

Highly skilled and motivated IT Support Analyst with 7 years of experience providing comprehensive technical support to optimize IT operations and enhance user productivity. Possess strong problem-solving abilities, excellent interpersonal skills, and a track record of delivering exceptional customer service. Seeking a challenging position in an organization where I can utilize my expertise to ensure efficient IT infrastructure and resolve technical issues promptly.

EXPERIENCE

IT SUPPORT / ACCOUNTING CLERK

July 12, 2016- Present

EVB Bookkeeping Office | Batangas City 4200

Provided technical support to end-users, ensuring prompt resolution of hardware and software issues.

configure, and maintain operating systems, applications, and software updates.

Perform accounting and clerical functions to support supervisors, research, track, and resolve accounting problems.

TECHNICIAN / GRAPHIC ARTIST

May 2015 - June 2016

IT PC Works | Bauan, Batangas 4201

Diagnosed and resolved complex technical problems related to desktops, laptops, printers, and peripheral devices.

Provided hands-on support in installing, configuring, and maintaining hardware and software.

EDUCATION

TERTIARY

2012 - 2015

Information and Communication Technology

Colegio ng Lungsod ng Batangas Arrieta Road, Rizal Avenue Extension, Batangas City

ON JOB **TRAINING**

2014 - 2015

Inter PC Computer Store

2F Bay City Mall, 19 D. Silang, Poblacion, **Batangas City**

ASSESSMENT

Oct 21, 2014

Computer Hardware Servicing (NC II)

Cristo Rey Institute for Career Development 106 Rizal Ave, Barangay 22, Batangas City

REFERENCES

MARIEL DE CHAVEZ

Accounting Supervisor

EVB Bookkeeping Office

Hilltop Road, Kumintang Ibaba, Batangas City

Phone: 0956 234 2504 Email: marieldechavez44@gmail.com

KAREN ALEA

HR Supervisor

EVB Bookkeeping Office

Hilltop Road, Kumintang Ibaba, Batangas City

Phone: 0917 270 5629 Email: karenalea14@gmail.com

NOEMI BAGOT

Vibrant Wellness Trading Corporation

President Jose P. Laurel Hwy, Lipa City, Batangas Phone: 0921 951 4708 Email: noemikrizle19@yahoo.com

Accounting Head